Now if two companies are different companies,
both have different products, both Samson
Chairman's appointment
is one of the subscriptions,
subscribe
50, now here you must subscribe to a company,
and
subscribe where
subscribe to subscribe, the
second star is whose house,
so now let's compare these two policies,
now see here free
health check-up, see here you are
getting subscription under the policy, you should subscribe to
subscribe in 2009, if we
talk about abs then
subscribe,
if we talk about ambulance then up to ₹2000
but
subscribe and there is no
limit, see all of them, there are
AstroSage and but
see four to five times every week,
not all of the famous poems are covered, talk about and
subscribe the channel,
if
subscribe to
another company, subscribe no matter which
company you
subscribe to because it is
very important, so what happens, when you
take a policy, you look at the premium,
but when you are admitted in the hospital, then you
look at why am I not getting this,
why was my money taken, etc. etc.
Subscribe to the channel